(Syncro: F.B Cavalcante)
Look at me, Lockwood. Look at me.
看着我, Lockwood, 看着我
Giant octopuses don't just vanish into thin air.
巨型章鱼并没有消失在空气中
So you're some kind of expert, are you?
看来你是个专家啊, 是吗？
You can't turn your back on what you've done.
你做过的事情, 已经不能回头了
You have to tell me the truth.
你必须得跟我说实话
- You don't understand.  - Try me.
- 你不会明白的  - 试试
No, I don't feel in control.
不, 我觉得我有控制权
I feel old.
我觉得老了
- You're not safe here.
- I'm not safe anywhere.
- 你在这里不安全  - 我在哪里都不安全
- Shall we go back, then?
- Natasha.
- 那, 我们该回去吗？  - Natasha
Whatever happened on Sentinel Island isn't over.
不管哨兵岛上发生的是什么, 都还没有结束
You're part of it now, Lockwood.
It's part of you.
你现在是它的一部分了, Lockwood．它也是你的一部分
It's for that very reason, I can't go back.
正是因为这个原因, 我才不能回去
How long do you think my head would
stay connected to the rest of my body?
你觉得我的脑袋还能跟我身体的其它部位一起待多久？
But UNIT wouldn't...
但 UNIT 不会...
There are fairies at the bottom
of my garden too.
在我的花园底部也有很多小仙子
You're right.
你说得对
I tried to contain that thing...
我试图笼住那个东西...
Here.
这里
But all I did was give it a route back.
但我所做的事情其实是给了它一条路
All the more reason
why you should come with me.
那你就更应该跟我来了
I've made a terrible mistake.
我犯了一个严重的错误
Lockwood?
Lockwood?﻿
Mister Winslet.
Winslet 先生
Mister Winslet?
Winslet 先生?
Graham?
Graham?﻿
What are we doing out here
in our jim-jams again?
我们在外面做什么?fixme
Come along.
快过来
No.
不
It's coming back.
它回来了
It's coming back for me.
它回来找我了
No.
不
Thank you, Dalby.
谢谢你, Dalby
Sit down, Doctor Arnold.
坐下, Arnold 博士
My name is Palmer.
我的名字是 Palmer
You are in my custody now.
你现在在我的监管之下了
A lot's been happening,
Doctor Arnold.
发生了很多事情, Arnold 博士
Catch up.
补补课吧
New York Stock Exchange,
all systems wiped.
纽约证券交易所, 所有系统被抹掉了
NASDAQ's in free-fall.
纳斯达克在自由落体
Aeroflot flight 496 fell out of the sky
over Berlin, computer malfunction.
Aeroflot 的 496 航班在柏林上空飞出了天外, 电脑故障
Perth Australia, sixteen patients
in intensive care,
澳大利亚珀斯, 16 个病人进入重症监护
their respirators just happened to
turn themselves off at the same time.
他们的呼吸机停掉了，在同一时刻
Just what does this have to do with me?
这些跟我有什么关系
It started when Lockwood left Sentinel Island...
这都是在 Lockwood 离开哨兵岛的时候开始的
And it hasn't stopped.
而且还没有停止
In fact, it's getting worse.
事实上, 还在恶化
By the middle of next week
there won't be a computer left...
到下周中期, 就一台电脑也不剩了...
on the planet that hasn't malfunctioned.
全球的电脑全部都会工作不正常
And that doesn't even scratch the
surface of what's happening at Millhampton.
而这些跟 Millhampton 医院发生的事情比起来都是小巫见大巫
Are we smelling the coffee yet,
Doctor Arnold?
闻到烧咖啡的味道了吗，Arnold 博士？
Look what I found.
看看我找到了什么？
I thought it was best to let you sleep.
我一直觉得最好是让你睡觉
Yeah, sleep.
是啊, 睡觉
Dreams.
做梦
No, thank you.
不了, 谢谢你
I've got enough rubbish inside me
as it is without adding to it.
我体内已经有够多的垃圾了，不需要再加
It's out of you now.
它没在你里面了
Let's take stock, shall we?
我们来捋一下，好吗？
An ancient elemental force...
一股古老的自然力量...
Buried deep below the surface...
深埋在地表之下...
Waiting for a signal to re-emerge.
等着一个信号以东山再起
A paranoid and secretive...
一个偏执而秘密的...
Governmental paramilitary team...
政府半军事化小组...
Desperate to get its hands on me...
不顾一切地想要把我抓到手...
Well...
好吧...
What's inside me,
要的是在我体内的东西
before the enemy does.
抢在敌人之前
How am I doing so far?
我都做了些什么？
UNIT, the Nestenes,
I bet you never felt so popular.
又是 UNIT, 又是 Nestenes，我打赌你从未觉得如此受欢迎
Someone cut through the wrong cable
at the psychic exchange?
你们的通灵渠道被人切错电缆了？
Try something a little  more...
试试别的方法，比如更加...
Conventional.
传统的
No, wait.
不, 等等
There is something.
这里有事情
Friends.
朋友
Lockwood left the door
open for them, Doctor Arnold.
Lockwood 给他们留了门, Arnold 博士
Just when was it
you realised he'd changed sides?
你是什么时候发现他改变立场了？
Just before I was
dragged off by the ISD.
就在我被内部安全部拖出来的时候
You need me.
你需要我
Why should I help you,
我为什么要帮你,
when I've been wired up
in that dungeon of delights,
我被绑在那个地牢里
interrogated for three weeks solid?
被审讯了整整三个星期？
You're a close associate of Lockwood's.
你是 Lockwood 关系紧密的同事
Now, the question is...
现在的问题是...
Just how close?
有多紧密？
What do you want from me?
你想从我这里得到什么？
When we last met...
上次我们碰面的时候...
a seed was planted in your mind.
就将一颗种子种在了你的意识里
Your very...
你那非常..
Very special mind, Lockwood.
非常特别的意识，Lockwood
You're too kind.
你太好心了
It's been...
它一直在...
Germinating.
发芽...
Why are you investigating Lockwood?
你为什么在调查 Lockwood?
He's UNIT's best operative.
他是 UNIT 最好的特工
We're investigating him because his...
我们调查他是因为他的...
special abilities...
特殊能力...
are a two-way street.
那是一条双行道
He may have permanent access...
他可能有永久权限...
to the sum total of
UNIT's acquired wisdom...
可以访问 UNIT 所获取的所有智慧...
through a piece of hardware in his brain,
仅仅通过他大脑里的一小片硬件fixme
but that means someone,
somewhere in this great organisation...
但这就意味着某个人，在这个大机构里面某个地方...
is watching over his every thought.
在观察着他的每一个想法
Now listen to me, you stubborn old bastard.
听我说，你个顽固的老东西
Don't let that smooth-talking piece
of plastic let you wallow in self-pity.
别让那个巧舌如簧的塑料假人, 引导你沉溺于自怜中
Look into my mind.
进入我的意识看看
I know what it's like to be the outsider...
我知道当一个局外人是什么样的...
But we make ourselves outsiders.
但那是我们自己让自己成为局外人
The trick is to let people in.
关键是要让别人进来
Lockwood, I'm letting you in.
Lockwood，我让你进来
Where did that creature go?
那个生物去了哪里？
It hasn't gone, has it.
它还没走，是吧？
Lockwood, what have you done?
Lockwood，你做了什么？
Whose side are you on?
你到底是哪边的？
So you're psychic too.
看来你也是个通灵者
You read Natasha's mind.
你读了 Natasha 的思想
What did she mean?
她是什么意思
From what you're showing me,
Lockwood destroyed the thing.
从你显示给我的东西来看，Lockwood 摧毁了那个东西
Not destroyed, absorbed.
不是摧毁，是吸收了
Into his mind?
吸到他的意识里去了？
Pure mental energy.
完全的精神力量
So what happened in Millhampton,
when they got back to the mainland?
那他们回到大陆之后，Millhampton 医院发生了什么？
We don't know.
我们不知道
You've lost contact with Natasha.
你跟 Natasha 失去联系了
And Lockwood.
跟 Lockwood 也是
You...
你...
care for him.
关心他
Yes.
是的
Then help me.
那就帮我
Millhampton hospital.
Millhampton 医院
- Are you sure?  - Yes.
- 你确定吗？  - 是的
They're here.
他们在这里
Ramsay?
Ramsay吗?
- The team?  - No.
- 他的小组？  - 不是
Them.
是他们
The psychiatric unit.
精神科
Of course.
当然了
This is where we sent the
real Winslet to recuperate.
我们把真正的 Winslet 送到这里来调理
Clever bastards.
聪明的混蛋
Even you, Miss Alexander?
就连你，Alexander 小姐？
No one else could have kept me
as effectively hidden from UNIT
没有其他人可以把我如此有效地藏起来躲过UNIT
and be reeled in without even noticing.
被耍得团团转而浑然不觉
I was always the last boy
picked at games.
玩游戏时我总是最后一个被挑中的
Nothing changes.
什么都没变
If I can't get out...
如果我出不去...
then I'm not going to let you in!
你我也不打算让你们进去！
Time to sleep.
睡觉时间到了
To sleep.
该睡觉了
To dream.
做梦
Transmission cut out.
信号传输被切断了
Damn it.
该死
What did Palmer have to say,
anything useful?
Palmer 有什么要说的，有什么有用的吗？
Only the air contact was normal on
the west side of the town.
只说了镇子西边的空中联络还正常
Run for it!
快跑！
Open fire.
开火
Not quite what I expected.
跟我料想的不太一样
Nice to know all my research
paid off, though.
不过，知道自己的研究有价值，真好
- Come on, Sal.
- Just a minute. Power surge.
- 快点，Sal   - 等一下，能量涌动
Greyhound One to Greyhound Leader.
灰狗一号呼叫灰狗队长
Palmer, it's Ramsay.
Palmer, 我是 Ramsay.
We need rein...
我们需要增...
Looks like they've cranked up the power.
看来他们已经增强了能量
Run for it... Run for it, Sal!
快跑...跑啊，Sal！
Natasha?
Natasha?﻿
Ah, more dreams.
啊，又是梦
Amazing what goes on in the mind...
脑海里会发生什么，让人惊讶啊
At the point of death.
在此濒临死亡之时
Lockwood, wake up.
Lockwood，醒醒
We've got to get out of here.
我们必须得离开这里
You don't remember what happened.
你不记得发生了什么
Lockwood, please.
Lockwood，求你了
You can't distract me.
你没法分散我的注意力
You're only a dream.
你只是一个梦
I wonder who else I shall dream about?
我好奇我还会梦到谁？
Oh, Palmer. Have you seen Ramsay?
噢，Palmer。你见到 Ramsay 了吗？
What about the rest of your team?
你小组的其他人呢？
Oh, running behind schedule, are we?
噢，我们落后于原定计划了，是吧？
Got to find Lockwood.
去找到 Lockwood
That's what we're here for, isn't it?
那是我们到这里来的原因，是吧？
Look, you asked me to help you...
看，你请求我帮助你...
We must find Lockwood.
我们必须找到 Lockwood
The others have arrived.
其他人已经到了
I knew he'd come.
我知道他会来的
You have a connection with him.
你跟他之间有链接
He reads your thoughts.
他能读你的想法
Are you sensing something?
你感觉到什么了吗？
Natasha?
Natasha?﻿
Maybe you're not tuning into her,
but she's tuning in to you.
也许你没有调到她的频道，但她已经调到了你的
Lockwood.
Lockwood.﻿
More dreams... only dreams...
还是梦...只有梦...
Lockwood.
Lockwood.﻿
You know you can't resist us.
你知道你无法抵抗我们的
Your breath smells, Mister Winslet.
你有口臭，Winslet 先生
Like rubber.
像橡胶一样
You are like us.
你跟我们很像
Linked to a greater intelligence...
与一个更高级的智慧相连
And yet...
同时也是...
part of it.
它的一部分
You rely on it...
你依赖它...
It is part of you.
它也是你的一部分
You communicate with it.
你与它交流
You can't shut it out, Lockwood.
你没法把它关在外面, Lockwood
If you want the implant,
如果你想要那个植入物
you could always crack
my skull open and cut it out.
你总可以破开我的头盖骨，把它取出来
But then it wouldn't be of any
use to you, would it?
但那样的话它对你也没有什么用了，是吧？
Needs a mind...
需要一个大脑...
to operate it.
来操作它
Sorry, old chap.
对不起，老家伙
Nice try.
很好的尝试
Any chance of a cup of tea?
有可能来杯茶吗？
Soon, Lockwood.
快了，Lockwood
Soon.
快了
Greyhound One to base.
灰狗一号呼叫基地
Greyhound One to base. Over.
灰狗一号呼叫基地。完毕
Do you think it's the same creature?
你觉得是同一个生物吗？
The one from Sentinel Island?
哨兵岛上的那个？
Possibly.
有可能
There's more of those creatures
on the planet, you know.
这个星球上还有很多这种生物，你知道吧
These sites have always been feared...
这些地方就一直被害怕着...
Revered and worshipped.
尊敬着, 崇拜着
Ancient sites linked by ley lines,
like the one on Sentinel Island.
这些古老遗迹都分布在雷线上，跟哨兵岛的这个一样
And this is another one,
is that what you're saying?
你的意思是，另外还有一个？
Perhaps.
也许
How are your psychic powers,
Mister Palmer?
你的超能力怎样了，Palmer 先生？
Have you sensed anything yet from
your protégé, Natasha Alexander the Great?
有没有从你的徒弟 Natasha Alexander 那里感觉到什么？
I'm waiting.
我在等待
What for, reinforcements?
等什么？增援？
We should have brought a bigger team
with us in the first place.
我们应该一开始就带一大票人马来的
Do you think that would have made
any difference?
你觉得那会有什么区别吗？
We're still alive, aren't we?
我们还活着，是吗？
- Yes, we are.
- So is Natasha, isn't she?
- 是的，我们是  - Natasha 也是，对吧？
I think so.
我觉得是
Anyone receiving? Over.
有人听到吗？完毕
Hello.
哈罗
This is Greyhound Leader.
Come in. Over.
这里是灰狗队长，请回话。完毕
Palmer! Palmer, is that you?
Palmer! Palmer，是你吗？
Ramsay!
Ramsay!﻿
This is Greyhound One.
这里是灰狗一号
Anyone receiving? Over.
有人听到吗？完毕
Ramsay!
Ramsay!﻿
Sal. Doctor Sal.
Sal。Sal 博士
Bit of a maverick.
有点独行侠
This is Greyhound Leader.
Come in. Over.
这里是灰狗队长，请回话。完毕
This other chap.
另外那个家伙
- Now who's he?  - Yes.
- 他是谁？  - 对
Who?
是谁？
No.
不
I think a little mystery is healthy...
我觉得神秘点更好...
Don't you, Mister Winslet?
你觉得呢，Winslet 先生？
This is Sal. Can you hear me?
这里是 Sal。你能听到吗？
- Sal, is that you?
- Yes, yes, it's me.
- Sal，是你吗？  - 是，是，是我
Oh God, James,
I thought you were dead.
噢上帝，James，我以为你们已经死了
Where are you?
你在哪儿？
Listen, there's a kind...of energy barrier.
听我说，这里有某种...能量屏障
I think they've cut off the entire town.
我觉得它们把整个镇子与外界切断了
We can't get out.
我们出不去
I've come back as far as the hospital.
我往回一直走到了医院
There's a lot of Auton activity here.
这里有很多 Auton 出没
I'm going to take a look...
我打算去看一看...
find out what they're up to.
搞明白它们要干什么
Quite a lot...
非常多...
Mister Ramsay.
Ramsay 先生
Where exactly is it, James?
具体在哪里，James？
Can you give us your position
so we can get to you? Over.
能把你的位置给我们吗？我们好去找你。完毕
North west of the city centre.
市中心的西北部
On the outskirts.
在郊区
Sal?
Sal?﻿
Sal, come in. Over!
Sal, 听到没。完毕
How do you find your dream now...
现在你如何找到你的梦...
Lockwood?
Lockwood?﻿
Good.
很好
You're trying so very hard,
aren't you, Lockwood?
你努力得很辛苦啊，是吧，Lockwood？
But for what?
但为了什么？
The miserable speck of
cosmic dust you call home?
宇宙尘埃的可怜斑点而已，还被称作家
No.
不
No, I don't think so.
不是，我不这么想
For pride...
为着骄傲...
Medals, pats on the back
from your worthless superiors?
奖章吗？抑或让你那些毫无价值的上级可以怕拍你的背？
No.
不
No, that's not your...
不，那不是你的...
Style!
风格！
I'll huff...
我一会儿吸气...
And I'll puff...
一会儿吹气...
And I'll blow...
我要吹倒...
Your house...
你的房子
In.
(出自童话故事《三只小猪》里面大灰狼的台词)
Granny...
奶奶...
what trite cultural references you have.
你应有的故事还真是陈腐
Never were any good at being human...
从来不擅长扮演人类
Were you?
是吧？
The form suffices...
这个皮囊足够了...
But it is...
Constraining.
It never fails to surprise me...
它总是让我感到惊讶...
How humans can live in
something so...
人类怎么能够活在这么...
Obsolete...
陈旧
And...
而且...
Small.
狭小的躯体里
The form suffices.
这个皮囊足够了
You are an insect, Lockwood.
你就是只虫子，Lockwood
You think your existence will
make one iota of difference
你以为你的存在会带来一丝丝的区别
to our colonisation of this world, when we
have waited a thousand million years....
我们在这个世界的殖民，已经等待了十亿年...
Seen the suns of million
systems grow old and die,
见过百万星系的太阳变老死去
watched life crawl from the slime
看过亿万世界的生命从烂泥里爬起来
and stand on its hind legs
on a trillion worlds?
学会用后腿站立
We are time, Lockwood...
我们就是时间，Lockwood
And you...
而你...
are but...
不过是...
a nano-second...
一纳秒...
in the history...of my...species
在我们种族的历史中
Dream away, Lockwood.
做梦去吧，Lockwood
Dream away.
做梦去吧
Dawn...
黎明...
A new dawn...
一个新的黎明...
will soon be here.
很快就会到来
Natasha?
Sergeant Ramsay, isn't it?
Ramsay 中士，是吗？
What happened to you?
你发生什么事了？
Sentinel Island...
哨兵岛...
The church...
教堂...
We got back to the mainland.
我们回到了大陆
Is Lockwood still alive?
Lockwood 还活着吗？
Yes, I think so.
是的，我觉得是
You think I'm an Auton.
你觉得我是个 Auton
Would you know if you were?
如果你是你会知道吗？
Would you tell me?
你会告诉我吗？
Does that think work on humans?
Well, let's find out.
那, 我们去探究明白
You all right?
你没事吧？
I'm fine.
我没事
So what does that prove?
那说明什么？
I don't know.
我不知道
It shouldn't have affected you.
应该没有感染你
But it did, didn't it?
但已经感染了, 是吧？
It's what, head north west?
Not exactly hurrying, are they?
他们似乎并不太着急, 是吧？
Just gently nudging us in the right direction.
只是温和地想把我们驱赶到正确的方向上
Now...
现在
Natasha...
Natasha...﻿
Bring Ramsay to us.
把 Ramsay 带我们这里来
What the hell are you doing?
你们在这里搞什么鬼？
Well done. Well.
做得好, 很好
Please don't struggle, Natasha.
请不要挣扎, Natasha
Stay with us.
跟我们待在一起
What is it?
是什么？
It's Natasha.
是 Natasha
She's with them.
她跟它们一边的
Not exactly.
并不像是
Voices.
声音
- Thousands of voices.  - What do you mean?
-  几千个声音  - 你什么意思?
The town, the people.
整个镇子, 所有人
All of them.
他们全部
Anguish,
苦闷
Pain.
疼痛
Break the link with Natasha. Break it!
断开与 Natasha 的连接, 断开它
No.
不
You stupid bastard, don't you see?
你个愚蠢的混蛋, 还没明白吗？
They've got to you through
your psychic link with Natasha.
它们可以通过你与 Natasha 的精神连接找到你
You're just like Lockwood.
你跟 Lockwood 一样
You've sold out without knowing it.
你被卖了都不知道
They must have wanted you to come here.
它们肯定一直都想要你来这里
That's why I'm here.
那就是我来这里的原因
What?
什么？
You knew this was going to be a trap?
你早知道这将是一个陷阱？
You'd rather I'd authorise
strategic nuclear action
你更愿意我授权进行战略核打击
and wipe this city off the map?
把这个小城从地图上抹掉？
Do you honestly think that would have worked?
你真的认为那个已经起作用了？fixme
And what about Lockwood?
那 Lockwoord 怎么办？
What about Natasha?
Natasha 呢？
Maybe they were relying on your...
也许它们还指望...
connection with her?
你与她之间的连接？
And through Lockwood to
every computer network in the world.
通过 Lockwood 连接到这个世界的每一个电脑网络
You finally see the bigger picture.
你终于看见大局了
Why do I suddenly feel like a small piece
on a very big chess board?
为什么我突然觉得自己像是一个很大的棋局里面的一个小兵？
Natasha?
Natasha?﻿
You're back.
你回来了
What happened to Ramsay?
Ramsay 怎么了？
Ramsay, Sal, Palmer,
they're coming to see you.
Ramsay, Sal, Palmer, 他们都来看你了
Sal?
Sal?﻿
Palmer?
Palmer?﻿
I mustn't ask questions.
我不能提问
I'm dreaming...
我在做梦...
And I must never...
而且我永不应该...
Wake up.
醒来
We all have to wake up sometime.
我们都有要醒来的时候
You're only human after all, Lockwood.
毕竟你只是一个人类, Lockwood
Special, perhaps...
有点特殊, 也许是...
With alien technology embedded in your mind...
脑袋里面嵌有外星科技...
Giving you access to so much knowledge...
可以让你访问如此之多的信息...
But you're still only human.
但你还是只是一个人类
I've always felt a bit of a non-starter...
我一直觉得有点碌碌无为...
In the human race.
fixme
It's only a matter of time.
这只是时间问题
I can see them.
我可以看到他们
- No.  - Friends.
- 不  - 朋友们
I knew he'd come.
我知道他回来
Get out!
出去！
I'm driving!
我来开！
- No, you don't understand.
- It's a trap, James.
- 不, 你不明白  - 这是个陷阱, James
He's known all along.
他一直都知道
He's led us into a bloody trap.
他把我们带入了这个血腥的陷阱
Get in. Get in!
进去, 进去！
I've had enough of this psychic crap.
我已经受够了这些通灵者的鬼话
The Autons.
是 Autons
Bastard. You sold us out.
混蛋, 你出卖了我们
It's the hospital.
是医院
We've got to go there.
我们得到那里去
Are you absolutely sure?
你绝对确定吗？
Yes.
是的
Too late.
太迟了
They're going to kill us.
它们要杀了我们
No...
不...
I don't think they are.
我不觉得他们会
Shut up.
闭嘴
Listen...
听着...
They've had plenty of opportunities already.
他们已经有了很多机会
They could have finished us off
a half a dozen time by now,
迄今为止, 他们已经有不下半打机会可以灭掉我们
but they haven't, have they?
但他们没有, 对不?
Well, don't you see?
怎样, 明白了吧？
Well, look.
好, 看
Look at them.
看看他们
They can't do it.
他们不会的fixme
They can't kill us.
他们不会杀我们
What the hell gives you that idea?
什么鬼给了你这个想法？
They tried to kill me, didn't they?
他们曾经试图杀死我, 是不是？
No, wait, James, he's right.
不, 等等, James, 他是对的
They have stopped.
它们停下来了
It's because they need us alive.
因为它们需要我们活着
They must do.
他们肯定是
But why?
但为什么？
What's so special about us?
我们为什么这么特别？
If we've any chance
whatsoever of stopping them...
如果我们有什么机会可能阻止他们...
that's exactly what we've got
to find out, isn't it?
那就是我们得去搞明白的事情, 对吧？
Come on...
快点...
- Let's say hello to them, shall we?
- After you, Mister Palmer.
- 我们来跟它们打声招呼吧, 好吗？  - 你先来, Palmer 先生
Shall we go?
我们走吗？
Palmer!
Palmer!﻿
You all right?
你没事吧？
Difficult to say.
很难说
Did you hear those voices?
你听到那些声音了吗？
- Any idea where we are?  - No.
- 知道我们在哪里吗？  - 不知道
But look what I found.
看看我找到了什么？
God, I hoped you'd come and find me, Ross.
上帝, 我期望你来找到我, Ross
I knew you would.
我就知道你会的
How could I not come looking for you?
我怎么会不来找你？
Always in each other's minds.
一直在彼此的心中
What have they tried to do, Natasha?
他们试图做什么, Natasha？
It's the real Winslet.
这是真正的 Winslet
The one the Nestenes copied in the first place?
就是一开始就被 Nestenes 复制了的那个？
What the hell's he doing here?
见鬼他在这里做什么？
I thought he was dead.
我以为他已经死了
He was in a coma for about a year,
他昏迷了差不多一年
Then he came out of it.
然后苏醒了
Of course.
当然是了
Millhampton Psychiatric Hospital.
Millhampton 精神病医院
The life came again.
fixme
They said it wouldn't come back...
他们说它不会再回来了
The doctors and nurses.
医生和护士们
They said I was asleep...
他们说我睡着了...
That I'd woken up.
然后我醒了
But it did come back.
Am I asleep again?
我又睡着了吗？
Why can't I wake up?
为什么我无法醒来？
What have they dredged him up for?
fixme
And what are we doing here?
我们又在这里做什么？
And where's that bastard Palmer?
Palmer 那个混蛋又去哪里了？
Come on, Natasha.
快点, Natasha
You can fight it.
你可以对抗它的
I know your mind's strong enough.
我知道你的意识足够强大
Tell me!
告诉我！
Listen to me.
听我说
We've got to find Lockwood...
我们得找到 Lockwood...
before the Nestene energy starts
flowing through his implant.
赶在 Nestene 能量开始流过他的植入物之前
Where is he!
他在哪里！
Doctor Arnold.
Arnold 博士
As a matter of fact, I have found a large number of
事实上, 我发现了一大批
crates with the same serial code.
有着同样编码的板条箱
Triple A stroke RH stroke 2961.
AAA/RH/2961
Some of them have the letters...
其中一些上面还有字母
A.U.T.O.N
A.U.T.O.N﻿
written on them.
上面写着
I'm told.
跟我说过了
Auton.
Auton.﻿
But I couldn't...
但我不能...
think what...
想那些...
I couldn't see...
我看不到...
I couldn't.
我不能
I could see everything it could see...
我可以看到它能看见的所有东西...
Like a nightmare.
像一个噩梦
Who's Lockwood?
Lockwood 是谁？
Lockwood?
Lockwood﻿?
Where is he? Have you seen him?
他在哪儿？你们见过他吗？
He, he is...
他, 他是...
He is dying.
他要死了
Dying?
要死了?
What do you mean? What have they done to him?
你什么意思？他们把他怎么样了？
Where is he?
他在哪儿？
He, he's...
他, 他已经...
He's asleep.
他已经睡着了
He can't wake up.
他无法醒过来
But if he doesn't wake up...
但如果他不醒过来...
He'll die.
他会死
Lockwood...
Lockwood...﻿
Absorbed the energy
他吸收了所有能量
of the creature on Sentinel Island...
从哨兵岛那个生物那里
But it broke free.
但它跑掉了
It's...
它被...
Buried...
埋藏得...
Deep...
很深...
They need me.
他们需要我
Awakening.
正在苏醒
Awakening?
苏醒？
What do you mean, awakening?
你什么意思, ＂苏醒＂？
Dreams...
梦
And nightmares.
和恶梦
I'm listening.
我在听
He's...
他是...
He's your friend.
他是你的朋友
Yes...
是的...
Of course he is.
他当然是
He's a one-off.
他是一次性的
Do you know where he is?
你知道他在哪儿吗？
Bring them here.
把他们带过来
Destroy the others.
消灭其他人
No!
不！
What is it?
怎么了？
What now?
现在怎样？
My mind's not strong enough...
他的意识不够强...
But yours is.
但你的可以
They sensed your mind in mine.
他们在我的意识里面觉察到了你的
We haven't got much time.
我们没有太多时间
Read me.
读吧
I can't keep this up for ever.
我不能一直撑着这个fixme
- You know where he is. Now go!
- Not without you.
- 你知道他在哪里．赶紧走！  - 你不走我也不走
I'm not strong enough to.
我不够强了
Please go.
请走吧
Hello, Sal.
哈罗, Sal
Lockwood.
Lockwood﻿
More dreams.
又是梦
No, not dreams.
不, 不要梦了fixme
James and I are real enough.
James 和我都是完全真实的
You're real.
你也是真实的
Sal...
Sal...﻿
What have you done?
你做了什么？
What?
什么？
No...
不...
No!
不!
Thank you, Doctor Arnold.
谢谢你, Arnold 博士
Palmer! What the hell's going on?
Palmer! 见鬼这是怎么了？
We were right.
我们说对了
They are using Lockwood's implant.
他们在利用 Lockwood 的植入物
Using it as a means
Of transmitting their energy.
把它用作传输他们能量的手段
Awakening.
苏醒
- What!  - Awakening.
- 什么！  - 苏醒
Lockwood's been trying to keep them
out of his mind all this time.
Lockwood 一直将他们抵制在他的意识之外
They tried to use Natasha's psychic abilities...
他们又试着用 Natasha 的通灵能力...
To break his resolve...
来攻破他...
But it didn't work.
但没其作用
But they sensed in me...
但他们觉察到了我...
Psychic powers that even Natasha didn't possess.
连 Natasha 都没有的通灵能力
They thought I'd do it for them...
他们觉得我会帮他们完成...
But it was you two...
但你们两个...
His friends.
才是他的朋友
And now we've buggered everything up.
现在我们把一切都搞砸了
We're activating a billion Nestene creatures
我们正在激活一百万个 Nestene 生物
buried throughout your world.
都是原本躲藏在你的世界地下的
They're coming back to life.
他们正在复活
Awakening.
在苏醒
You have served your purpose.
你们的使命已经完成了
You are no longer necessary.
不再需要你们了
I won't let you use my mind.
我不会让你使用我的意识的
Not again.
不再可以了
I won't let you!
我不会允许你的！
Get close to him.
往他靠近
Right hand button, three times.
右手按钮, 按三次
Oh, Lockwood, no!
噢, Lockwood, 不！
That's the trouble with dreams.
这是梦的问题
However nice they are...
不管它们有多美
You always have to wake up.
你还是得醒
It's over...
都结束了
Did you ever stop to consider
the risk to Lockwood?
你就没有停下来想一下对 Lockwood 的风险？
Your best operative,
他是你最好的特工
UNIT's star performer...
UNIT 明星人物...
that's what you made him believe.
fixme
And all the time you were planning
to drive him like a sheep through a mine field.
一直以来你都计划着, 把他像一头羊一样赶到雷区
It was the only course of action left open to me.
那是我唯一可以采取的手段
As far back as the warehouse we knew
早在仓库事件的时候我们就知道
Lockwood had been compromised.
Lockwood 已经被渗透了
He wasn't compromised,
he was fighting it.
他没被渗透, 他在同它抗争
Instead of sending spooks
to try and catch him out,
与其派些怪人来试探他抓他
did it never cross your mind
to ask him what was going on?
你有没有想到过来问问他是怎么一回事？
It may have escaped
your notice, Doctor Arnold,
有一点你可能没有注意到, Arnold 博士
but we've just been fighting a war.
但我们这是在打一场战争
There's no room for sentiment in a war.
在战争里面没有多愁善感的空间
You used my feelings...
你利用了我的感情
My feelings for Lockwood.
我对 Lockwood 的感情
You knew perfectly well
what taking me there would do.
你完全清楚把我带来的fixme
Yes.
是的
Get him out of my sight.
滚出我的视线